https://www.sikhhelpline.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Sikh Helpline respects the privacy of our users and is strongly committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy sets out how Sikh Helpline uses and protects information provided by you when you use this website. It does not apply to other Sikh Helpline products or services.
Sikh Helpline is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Sikh Helpline may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are updated with any changes.
1. What we collect and what do we do with the data
We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide on this website, which may include your name, address, email address, etc.
We use this information to communicate with you and to provide you with your requested service or product.
If you choose to opt-in to our mailing list, we may also use your contact information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
2. Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. Any personal information you provide to Sikh Helpline is kept on secure servers. Sikh Helpline uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures (a) to safeguard personal information against loss, theft, unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification; and (b) to ensure the integrity of the personal information.
3. Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links and leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over the other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
4. Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to reveal the information. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the contact address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
5. Disclosure of Personal Information
Sikh Helpline may disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary (a) to comply with the law or in response to a subpoena, court order, government request, or other legal process; (b) to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of Sikh Helpline or others; (c) to enforce any terms of service on this website; (d) to provide you with the services or products requested by you and to perform other activities related to such services and products, including billing and collection; (e) to provide you with information, special offers, or promotions from Sikh Helpline to which you consented; or (f) to operate Sikh Helpline‘s systems properly. Sikh Helpline makes reasonable efforts to limit disclosure of your personal information to its designated service providers in the same manner as set forth in this paragraph.
Facebook0Tweet0Pin0LinkedIn0
Quick AccessHome
Sikh Helpline News
Feedback About Sikh Helpline
COVID-19
PPE Fundraiser Page
50 mile Charity Bikeride
Be a Volunteer!
Charity Bikeride  (8)
Community News  (3)
Coronavirus  (15)
Coronavirus Sidebar  (10)
Feedback  (3)
MILES FOR PPE  (8)
Sikh Helpline  (11)
Sikh Helpline News  (36)
Testimonials  (6)
Bullying and Discrimination  (7)
Depression and Anxiety  (2)
Domestic Abuse  (2)
Grooming and Conversions  (10)
Relationship Issues  (2)
Sexual Abuse  (1)
Substance Abuse  (5)
No comments found.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website.
ACCEPT
MORE INFO
